export const dataStructure = [
    {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to find the largest and smallest number in a linked list?',
        options: ['Recursion', 'Iteration', 'Both Recursion and iteration', 'Impossible to find the largest and smallest numbers'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array',
        options: ['Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance.', 'It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List', 'Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists', 'All of the above'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to find the largest and smallest number in a linked list?',
        options: ['Recursion', 'Iteration', 'Both Recursion and iteration', 'Impossible to find the largest and smallest numbers'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array',
        options: ['Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance.', 'It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List', 'Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists', 'All of the above'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to find the largest and smallest number in a linked list?',
        options: ['Recursion', 'Iteration', 'Both Recursion and iteration', 'Impossible to find the largest and smallest numbers'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array',
        options: ['Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance.', 'It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List', 'Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists', 'All of the above'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to find the largest and smallest number in a linked list?',
        options: ['Recursion', 'Iteration', 'Both Recursion and iteration', 'Impossible to find the largest and smallest numbers'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array',
        options: ['Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance.', 'It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List', 'Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists', 'All of the above'],
        answer: '3'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following methods can be used to find the largest and smallest number in a linked list?',
        options: ['Recursion', 'Iteration', 'Both Recursion and iteration', 'Impossible to find the largest and smallest numbers'],
        answer: '2'
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of the following points is/are true about Linked List data structure when it is compared with array',
        options: ['Arrays have better cache locality that can make them better in terms of performance.', 'It is easy to insert and delete elements in Linked List', 'Random access is not allowed in a typical implementation of Linked Lists', 'All of the above'],
        answer: '3'
    }
]